Hello, and welcome to "Supercharged."
嗨，欢迎来到“增压”。
I'm Paul.
我是保罗
Aah!
这就是为什么我们不直接显示。
The show where I take the sites that you've submitted,
在此程序中，我将访问您提供的站点，然后进行浏览。
And I look for performance issues,
寻找性能问题，
and I recommend some fixes.
他建议进行一些改革。
That's the show.
这是程序。
Welcome!
欢迎光临！
Today I have Player FM.
今天我有播放器FM。
And Player FM is an interesting one for me
这是一个有趣的网站
because it's run by Mike [? Marmov ?] who
现在是其导演迈克·马诺夫（Mike Marmoff）
is a small business owner, and so he's
他是一家小公司的所有者，
dealing with the sites and the app that he's built
因此，它可以处理其构建的网站和应用
and lots of other things besides.
还有很多其他事情。
And so for him I suspect that performance is important,
所以我希望表现对他很重要，
but it's not necessarily what's on his mind day to day.
但这并不一定是日常工作。
He's just trying to run his business and do well there.
他只是想把生意做好。
So it was an opportunity to look at something where
所以这是一个看东西的机会
the constraints are little bit different, at least
限制略有不同的地方，至少
from the business side.
从商业方面。
Serious performance work about to take place.
严肃的性能工作即将开始。
Hmm, yes, one has goggles.
是的，这就是为什么我要戴防护眼镜。
Not strictly necessary, but they do make you look fabulous.
没必要，但是它们使您看起来很棒。
I have the home page up on screen here.
我在这里有主屏幕。
And what I wanted to do was just do
我首先要做的是
a WebPagetest first and foremost, and have a quick look
在整个WebPagetest网站上测试性能并快速浏览
and just see if there's anything quick and easy to fix in there.
并寻找快速且易于修复的任何内容。
And I've gone to the filmstrip view which you can get if you
您选择可以选择的电影视觉模式
chick-- check, chick, check--
如果女孩选择女孩，请选择
If you check the box that says, capture video,
如果选择它旁边的框，则捕获视频
it'll capture a video.
将拍摄视频。
And that will give you the filmstrip view which
这将给您电影般的视觉
is what we're looking at here.
您在这里寻找的是什么。
The thing I notice, first of all,
一开始我注意到的是
is that when you look at where the first paint happens--
那是当您看第一张图纸的位置时-
which is here.
他在这
It's actually that green line there on the waterfall,
实际上，瀑布上有绿线，
I believe.
我想
You can see there's actually blocking on a few things.
您会看到有几处障碍。
There's the fonts.
有字体。
There's the page CSS which is quite big as well.
页面CSS也很大。
It's like 100K or so.
差不多100公斤。
So you'd really feel this on 3G.
因此，您将在3G上感受到它。
Now I'm not doing it on 3G today.
我今天不在研究3G。
Because I figure for most people, if they're on mobile,
因为对于大多数人来说，如果他们在移动设备上，
they've probably got the app, for example.
例如，他们最有可能拥有该应用程序。
So I opted to go with a desktop audience here.
因此，我想介绍计算机用户。
So we have-- the page comes in.
因此，我们有了-页面打孔。
Then there's the CSS.
然后是CSS。
There is an image.
有照片。
There's the JavaScript.
这是JavaScript。
There's the fonts which then need to be transferred.
有些字体需要移动。
There seems to be some-- what's this?
似乎有些东西-那是什么？
There's a Google JavaScript client there,
那里有一个Google JavaScript客户端，
and then there's the web fonts.
然后是网格线。
And then eventually it goes right-- now
然后最后正确承担
I've got enough to render.
现在-我有足够的工作量。
So I think the first thing I'd say
所以我想我要说的第一件事
is, it's a critical rendering path.
这是一条敏感的渲染路径。
Our job here is to [? interline ?] some styles.
我们在这里的工作是介绍一些模式。
Let's have a look-- see if there are any in the page source.
看一下-查看页面源中是否有任何模式。
So I suspect there aren't any.
好吧，我认为没有模式。
Because they'd be here if they were.
因为我会在这里找到他们的。
And I think that's probably one of the options
我认为这是选择之一
that we have here is to try and reprioritize
我们在这里正在重新安排优先事项
the page load to try and get critical rendering path done.
加载页面以尝试获取敏感的渲染路径。做完了
But even with that in play, there's
但是即使发生这种情况，
something quite interesting about this home page,
这个首页有趣的是，
which is the scrolling performance.
这是滚动效果。
Let me bring up DevTools.
让我打开DevTools。
And this has recently changed, its seems.
这似乎最近有所改变，
And you can find the old school rendering tools
您可以找到旧的渲染工具
under more tools and then rendering settings.
在“更多工具”下，然后单击“渲染设置”。
And then you can go to enable paint flashing.
然后启用涂料闪烁。
Flash.
快闪
As you scroll, you'll see that the whole page goes green.
导航时，每个页面变为绿色。
And that basically means the whole page is painting.
这意味着每页都在绘制。
And also it's painting-- you see it's pretty slow to paint.
您还可以绘画-您会看到绘画进展缓慢。
So let's have a look at why.
因此，让我们看一下原因。
We're in the timeline.
我们按计划进行。
We can hit record, and we'll do a scroll test
我们按下注册，然后测试通过
in the background.
在后台。
Stop scrolling.
停止滚动。
And you see these red triangles here in the corner
你会在角落看到这些红色三角形
is basically where Chrome is telling you that it's not
Chrome告诉您它无法
able to hit 60 frames a second.
达到60 fps。
And it's a little bit forgiving around the 60 frames
而且大约可以容纳60帧
a second mark.
第二个标志。
I can't remember the exact numbers.
我记不清这些数字了。
But we are at eight frames a second, 10, seven.
但是我们每秒八帧，十帧，七帧。
So for something that should be scrolling at 60 frames
因此，每秒应该通过60帧
a second, we're really struggling.
我们真的很痛苦。
And what we can do is we can have a look at why.
我们可以做的就是查看原因。
And you see these tile workers-- which are basically
您会看到瓷砖工人-他们是
the parts of Chrome that are doing the painting-- they're
镀铬零件-它们是
all very, very clogged up.
所有很多，非常堵塞。
So we can have a look in.
所以我们可以看看。
We can hit the w key on the keyboard-- which
我们可以按键盘上的w键
is like the zoom in-- and it says, rasterize paint.
缩放-书写点画图形。
And that correlates very closely with what we saw,
这与我们所看到的密切相关，
that sort of green paint that we saw earlier.
我们之前看到的绿色图形。
So let me see if we can figure out why.
因此，让我看看是否能找出原因。
And I'm betting it's the parallax thing that's
我敢打赌这与现场有关
going on, would be my guess because I've seen
发生这种情况，这是我的看法，因为我看到了
sites that do similar things.
网站做同样的事情。
So we'll just inspect that element.
因此，我们将首先检查这些元素。
See if we can bring that up.
因此，如果我们能带来这一点。
Section.
部分。是的
We have background position-- 50.
我们的墙纸网站-50。
Blah blah blah.
等等等等。
So these all look like-- yeah they're
所以这一切看起来像-是的
being changed by the JavaScript.
由JavaScript更改。
You can see that you can watch the numbers change up here.
您可以看到您可以在此处看到数字的变化。
And the problem we have is that this is causing it to paint.
我们面临的问题是，这使它们成为油漆。
What we'll do is, we'll stop it doing this.
我们将要做的是，阻止它这样做。
And then I will show you how you can actually
然后我会告诉你如何
have a proper look at this in more detail yourself.
详细了解此内容。
So what I'll do is-- I'm just going
所以我要做的是
to set background position to be-- I'm
我将选择背景位置为-
just going to do-- what has he got?
-他有什么？
Like roughly 50%, zero.
大约50％，零。
And I'm going to put important on it
我会重视他们
just so that it never changes.
永不改变。
And those images are fixed right now.
这些图像现已确认。
So when they're fixed-- when we scroll, what's going to happen
所以当它证明-当我们通过时，发生的是-
is-- Chrome's going to go, well that's got to be there still
Chrome将会，这意味着它仍然存在
on the page, so it paints it again and again
在页面上，一遍又一遍地绘制它
and again and again.
一遍又一遍。
So what we can do is we can find, presumably, a [?
所以我们能做的就是找到
background attachment: fixed. ?] Yes here it is.
后部附件：固定。是的，这些都是。
I'm just going to toggle that off for a second.
我会停一秒钟。
So that they scroll with the page content.
传递页面的内容。
Now even though these styles are being
现在虽然页面
updated by the page in the JavaScript,
这些模式出现在JavaScript中，
they're not going to change the actual position
他们不会更改实际位置
because we changed it to important and don't move.
因为我们将其更改为重要并且不动。
So with that all in place, let's now go back over here
一切准备就绪，让我们回到这里
and we're going to hit record, and we're going to scroll.
我们将记录下来，我们将继续前进。
And we are, pretty much, back to 60 frames a second.
然后他又回到了每秒60帧。
There are few things like these image decodes and so on.
有一些类似图像解码之类的东西。
But the main gist of it is that by just not doing
但是本质不是要做
that background position scroll thing,
通过传递该背景位置，
we're in a lot better state.
我们的状况更好。
Yes!
是的
So awhile ago, I wrote this post about parallaxing.
前一段时间，我写了这篇有关理论家差异的出版物。
And in here is the option two, which
这是第二种选择，
is what I'd suggest-- it would be worth
我建议的-值得
doing here for Player FM.
为FM Player完成。
It's using DOM elements rather than background position.
是使用DOM元素代替背景位置。
Put those images onto their own element,
将这些图像放在自己的元素上，
and then use a 3D transform-- or even a 2D transform--
然后使用3D适配器-或2D适配器-
with something like, will change our [? translateZ(0 ?].
看起来像的东西会改变Z的穿透力
That's right, I'll hack if necessary.
没错，如有必要，我会进行介绍。
We're quite pragmatic around these parts.
对于这些部分，我们非常实用。
And you can here see what it's like
在这里您可以看到它的样子
if you just use that approach.
如果您使用该方法。
And what I'll do is, I'll do a timeline recording
我要做的是，我要记录时间表
just so that you see it.
只是看到它。
And scroll up and down.
上下滚动。
And it's pretty much 60 frames a second everywhere.
而且几乎到处都是每秒60帧。
And the reason it's 60 frames a second is because we're using
之所以是60 fps，是因为我们使用适配器。
And transforms we can do-- if it's on its own layer,
我们可以制造变压器-如果他们在他们的班上。
it can be done by the GPU, and that's extremely fast.
GPU可以做到这一点，这非常快。
So you can do 60 frames a second parallax effects.
因此，您可以每秒执行60帧具有不同效果的帧。
I think right now the way that it's
我怀疑你这样
being done on this page where it uses
这是在使用该页面的页面上完成的
background position, that's not going to be 60 frames a second.
背景位置，不会达到60 fps。
But when you can do it with a transform and have it
但是，当您使用适配器并使其完成时
operate on individual elements, that you can do.
处理单个项目，您可以执行此操作。
I can't juggle.
我无法操纵。我不能
I don't even know why I tried.
我不知道我没有尝试过。
All right, cool.
好的，我们完成了主页。
So what we'll do is we'll actually switch across,
我们将要做的就是改变
and we'll look at a details page--
我们将看一下详细信息页面-
as in for one of the series.
如系列之一。
And it just so happens I have exactly the right
我有适当的网址
URL up my sleeve, which involves two idiots--
在我的袖子里，里面装着傻瓜
me and Wakey Jakey Vegas, doing a nice
Wakey Jackie和我，我们正在做有关HTTP 203的精彩播客。
It's a subtle plug.
这是一个微妙的组成部分。
If you just pay the slightest attention,
如果少注意一点
it's almost like I'm saying, subscribe subscribe
就像我说的，订阅订阅
subscribe subscribe subscribe subscribe subscribe.
订阅订阅订阅订阅订阅。
This time we don't have any, I don't think,
这次我们没有任何东西，我不认为，
any scroll performance issues particularly.
导航性能没有问题。
Basically because the page is fairly static.
因为页面是相当静态的。
However, I think what we can do is,
但是，我认为我们能做的，
we can have ourselves another sneaky peek at WebPagetest.
我们可以看一下WebPagetest网站。
So let's pop that in there.
因此，让我们在这里打开它。
Do that.
做这个。
We'll do it on Chrome cable.
我们将在Chrome电缆上进行此操作。看起来不错
Seems good.
捕获视频，以便您进行电影视觉。
Oh yes, we're waiting.
是的，我们正在等待。
What's he going to do next?
他下一步将做什么？
Yes, that's right.
是的，没错。
He's going to jettison his career.
会放弃他的职业。
Here are the results.
这是结果。
We've switched up to a one tenth of a second for the intervals.
我们切换到十秒间隔。
And yet, similar kind of story-- I think-- to the homepage.
但是，主页也有相同的故事-我想-。
Except this time, we look-- to my eye--
但是这一次，我们-目睹了-
like we're blocking on the, obviously, the page.
当然，好像我们在阻止页面一样。
But then there's some JavaScript,
但是有一些JavaScript，
and then there's some CSS-- bunch
然后是一些CSS
of image assets, which is fine.
一些资产图片，很好。有点期待。
But then there's web fonts, and then
但是然后有网格线，然后
only after the web fonts have arrived,
只有到达网格线之后，
do we actually do the initial paint.
我们进行初始绘制。
And yeah, actually, you can see if you're
是的，事实上，您可以看到
to look into one of these pages, you
我看了其中一页，
get that blank, white screen before the font
您会看到空白的空白屏幕
is actually available.
字体可用之前。
So that can be quite frustrating for users,
这可能会让用户感到沮丧，
depending on how long it takes for the font to come down.
取决于线条将需要出现多长时间。
One option is to have the font essentially not
一种选择是基本上不在那条线上-
be there-- use a system font.
使用系统字体。
And then try and get the web font for the next time.
然后尝试下次让您连接网络。
So lazy load it and then deal with it next time.
太懒得不能随身携带，下次再与他打交道。
That could be a bit of a challenge to orchestrate,
这可能很难组织。
which is hopefully where things like font display will help.
希望线宽之类的东西会有所帮助。
But for the time being, it might just
但是如今，有可能
be worth switching this font back out to a system font--
最好用系统线代替
if it is a web font, and it looks like it is.
如果是网络线，似乎是这样。
Or just using the web font for titles
或者只是使用网格线作为地址
and leaving the system font for the majority of the content.
剩下的内容留在系统行中。
There's a few things I would look
有些事情我想
at on both the homepage and the individual podcast pages.
看一下主页和各个播客。
And, you know, that's great.
太棒了
So don't forget you can submit your sites.
别忘了您可以提交位置信息。
Don't forget to subscribe.
不要忘记分享。
You should click that button.
您应该按此按钮。
That would be awesome.
那太好了。
And I will catch you next time.
下次见。
I haven't been allowed out of this room in three weeks.
我三个星期都不允许离开这个房间。
Put makeup on you before you go out on camera, you know.
拍摄前涂抹化妆品。
There, they said, Paul, you've got a shiny head.
他们说，保罗，你脑袋闪闪发亮。